Guide to the Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
- GaieLivraison (Box 3)
  Publisher: GaieLiveraison
  Publication City: Winnipeg, Manitoba
- Gaiety (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gali Company
  Publication City: Memphis, Tennessee
- GALA (Gay and Lesbian Awareness) (Box 3)
  Publication City: Stanford, CA
- GALA Gram: UCLA Gay and Lesbian Association (Box 3)
  Subject: College/University, Education, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: UCLA Gay & Lesbian Association
- GALA Nebraska: University of Nebraska-Lincoln Gay and Lesbian Alumni/ae Association (Box 3)
  Subject: College/University
  Publisher: UNL Gay and Lesbian Alumni/ae Association, Inc.
  Publication City: Lincoln, NE
- Gala News (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Alliance of Humboldt County
  Publication City: Eureka, CA
- GALA-GU News: Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association of Georgetown University (Box 3)
  Publisher: The Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association of Georgetown University
- GALAlumni--ND/SMC (Box 3)
  Subject: Education, College/University
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Alumni/ae of the University of Notre Dame and Saint Mary's College
  Publication City: Saint Paul, MN
- GALVANIZE! Gay and Lesbian Visibility Alliance (Box 3)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay
  Publisher: The Gay and Lesbian Visibility Alliance
  Publication City: Madison, WI
- GAPS (Gay Amateur Press Society) (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Men, Zine, Bear
  Publisher: Gay Amateur Press Society
  Publication Country: United State
- GATEScanner: Gay Association of Technicians, Engineers and Scientists (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay
  Publisher: Gay Association of Technicians, Engineers and Scientists
- Gay & Lesbian Awareness Week (1986) (Box 3)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Gay, Lesbian, Stanford University
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford
- Gay 80's: New York's First Gay & Lesbian Skills Exchange (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Education, Community
  Publisher: Gay 80's
- Gay Academic Union of New York City Newsletter (Box 3)
- Gay and Lesbian Alumni of Lawrence University (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay & Lesbian Alumni of Lawrence University
- Gay and Lesbian Community Yellow Pages (Box 3)
- Gay and Lesbian Media Workers Bulletin (Box 3)
  Subject: Mass media
- Gay Bards (Box 3)
  Subject: Literary, Gay
  Publisher: X-PRESS
- Gay Bookworm (Box 3)
  Publication City: St. Paul, MN
- Gay Catholic: Newsletter of Dignity/LA (Box 3)
  Subject: Religious: Catholic, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Dignity/L.A.
- Gay Community Appeal of Toronto Newsletter (Box 3)
  Publication City: Toronto, ON
- Gay Community Center (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gay Community Center of Baltimore
  Publication City: Baltimore, MD
- Gay Community Center (GCC) Newsletter (Seattle) (Box 3)
  Subject: Community, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gay Community Center (Seattle)
- Gay Community Center: Baltimore Pride 1999 (Box 3)
  Subject: Pride Parade, Gay, Lesbian, Community
- Gay Era (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Politics
  Publisher: Gay Era
  Publication City: Lancaster, PA
- Gay Fathers of Toronto (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay male, Parenting, Families
  Publisher: Gay Fathers of Toronto
- Gay Fathers San Diego (Box 3)
  Subject: Parenting, Families
  Publisher: Gay Fathers San Diego
  Publication City: San Diego, CA
- Gay Guide (Box 3)
- Gay Guide of the World (Box 3)
  Subject: Travel, Directory, Gay
- Gay Hawaii (Box 3)
  Subject: Community, News
  Publisher: Gay Hawaii
  Publication City: Honolulu, HI
- Gay Info (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay Info
  Publication City: Montreal, Quebec
- Gay Liberation Day (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Waller Press
- Gay Life (Box 3)
- Gay Life (Box 3)
  Publication City: (Reno, NV)
- Gay Life (Reno, NV) (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Community, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Lavender Press
  Publication City: Reno, NV
- Gay Lutheran (Box 3)
  Subject: Religious: Lutheran
  Publisher: Lutherans Concerned for Gay People
- Gay Market (Box 3)
  Publisher: Greater Gotham Business Council
- Gay Market Report (Box 3)
  Subject: Mass media, Business
  Publisher: Overlooked Opinions, Inc.
- Gay Media Alliance (Box 3)
- Gay Men's Domestic Violence Project Newsletter, The (Box 3)
  Subject: Anti-violence, Gay male, Gay, Gay health, Health
  Publication City: Cambridge, MA
- Gay Milwaukee (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Community
  Publisher: Ultra Ink, Inc.
- Gay News (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay Publishing Collective
  Publication Country: New Zealand
  Publication City: Auckland
- Gay News (Amsterdam) (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay International Press
  Publication Country: The Netherlands
  Publication City: Amsterdam
- Gay News (Chicago) (Box 3)
  Subject: Community, News, Gay
  Publisher: Gullivers Periodicals
- Gay News (Gay McGill Newsletter) (Box 3)
  Subject: College/University, Education
  Publisher: Gay McGill
  Publication City: Montreal, QC
- Gay Niagara News (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay Unity Niagra
  Publication City: Niagra Falls, ON
- Gay Nouveau, The (Greater Cincinnati's Gay News Journal) (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Community, Gay journal
  Publisher: Print Unlimited
  Publication City: Cincinnati, OH
- Gay Olympics Newsletter (Box 3)
  Subject: Community, Gay, Sports, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gay Olympic Games
- Gay Opinion (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Politics
- Gay People in Medicine Newsletter (Box 3)
  Subject: Medicine, Health, Gay health, Gay, Lesbian, Education, College/University
  Publisher: Gay People in Medicine Committee: American Medical Student Association
  Publication City: Schaumberg, IL
- Gay Pride (Box 3)
  Subject: Pride parade, Gay, Lesbian, Community, News
  Publisher: The Flying Nun (GAY ALLIANCE of San Francisco)
- Gay Renaissance Newsletter (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Literary, Community
  Publisher: Renaissance
- Gay Revolution Party (Box 3)
  Subject: Politics, News, Community, Gay, Lesbian, Literary, Zine, Prisoners, Feminist
  Publisher: Gay Revolution Party
- Gay Rights (Box 3)
- Gay SIGnificance (National Special Interest Group in MENSA) (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay SIGnificance (National Special Interest Group in MENSA)
- Gay Speakers Bureau (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Politics, Community, Community services
  Publisher: Gay Speakers Bureau
- Gay Teachers of Maryland Newsletter (Box 3)
  Publisher: Gay Teachers of Maryland
- Gay Times: Newsletter of the Gay Community Center (Box 3)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Community, News, Community services
  Publisher: Gay Community Center of Middletown
  Publication City: Middletown, NY
- Gay Travel (RSVP Gay Cruises) (Box 3)
  Subject: Travel, Gay
  Publisher: RSVP Travel Productions, Inc.
  Publication City: Minneapolis, MI
- Gay- Ways '69 (New York City Directory) (Box 3)
  Subject: Directory, Community, Gay, Gay male
  Publisher: Terrene Publications
- Gay World, The (A Complex of Gay Entertainment) (Box 3)
  Subject: Entertainment, Classifieds, Community, Erotica
  Publisher: Gay World
- Gay/Lesbian March Activists Cincinnati (GLAMA) News (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Gay, Lesbian, Community
  Publisher: Gay/Lesbian March Activists Cincinnati (GLAMA)
- Gaycon Press Newsletter (Box 3)
  Subject: Prisoners, Gay, Lesbian, Politics, Community, Community services
  Publisher: Gaycon Press
- Gaylaxicon: 1999 (Box 3)
  Subject: Entertainment, Calendar, Gay trekkies
  Publisher: Gaylactic Network
- Gaylife Magazine (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Community, Gay, Lesbian, Literary, Directory, Classifieds
  Publisher: Specialty Publications, Inc.
  Publication City: St. Louis, MO
- Gayme (Box 3)
  Subject: Entertainment, Community, Gay, Gay male, Literary, Book reviews, Gay journal
  Publisher: Zymurgy
- Gays For Equality (Winnipeg) (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Politics, Community, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gays for Equality (Winnipeg)
  Publication City: Winnipeg, MB
- Gayspeak (Newsletter of the Pikes Peak Gay Community Center) (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Community, Community services, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Pikes Peak Gay Community Center
  Publication City: Colorado Springs, CO
- Gayzette (Box 3)
  Subject: News, Gay
  Publisher: Heinz Meisenheimer
  Publication City: Koln
- Gay-Zette (Box 3)
  Subject: Community, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Gay-Zette (William C. Strauss)
  Publication City: Linwood, NJ
- Gay-zette (Box 3)
  Publication City: (Linwood, NJ)
- GBA Newsletter (Gay Business Association) (Box 4)
  Subject: Business, Gay, Community
  Publisher: Gay Business Association
- GCS Newsletter (Gay Community Services of Central Florida) (Box 4)
  Publisher: Gay Community Services of Central Florida
  Publication City: Winter Park, FL
- Gender News (Box 4)
  Publication City: (Port Hueneme, CA)
- Generation Next (Box 4)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, News
  Publisher: Generation Next Corp.
- Gertrude Stein Democratic Club: Gay Democrats of the Washington Metropolitan Area (Box 4)
  Subject: Politics, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gertrude Stein Democrat Club
- Gertrude's Notes (Box 4)
  Publisher: Gertrude Stein Society
  Publication City: New Orleans, LA
- GFLA: Gay Fathers Los Angeles Newsletter (Box 4)
  Publisher: Gay Fathers Los Angeles
- GGBA (newsletter of Golden Gate Business Association) (Box 4)
- Gibbous RISING (Box 4)
  Subject: News, Gay, Lesbian, Feminist
  Publisher: Gibbous RISING
  Publication City: Sacramento, CA
- gir(L) magazine (Box 4)
  Publisher: Allen-Branca & Associates, Inc.
  Publication City: Lighthouse Point, FL
- GLA Newsletter (Gays and Lesbians of Ames) (Box 4)
  Subject: Community, News, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: GLA (Gays and Lesbians of Ames)
  Publication City: Aimes, IA
- GLAD (Gay & Lesbian Advocates & Defenders) Annual Report (Box 4)
- Glad Day Newsletter (Box 4)
  Subject: Books, Catalog, News, Community
  Publisher: Glad Day Bookshop
- GLAD News (Gay and Lesbian Alliance of Greater Danbury) (Box 4)
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Alliance of Greater Danbury
  Publication City: Danbury, CT
- Glad Rag, The (Box 4)
  Publisher: GLAD
  Publication City: Halifax, NS
- GLAPN (Gay and Lesbian Archives of the Pacific Northwest) (Box 4)
  Subject: Community, History, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Archives of the Pacific Northwest (GLAPN)
  Publication City: Portland, OR
- GLID News (Gay and Lesbian Independent Democrats) (Box 4)
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Independent Democrats
- GLID Newsnotes (Gay and Lesbian Independent Democrats) (Box 4)
- Glowletter (The Newsletter of the Gay and Lesbian Organisation of the Witwatersrand) (Box 4)
  Subject: News, Community, International, South Africa
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Organisation of the Witwatersrand
  Publication Country: South Africa
  Publication City: Johannesburg
- GLPLA (Gay and Lesbian Parents of Los Angeles) Newsletter (Box 4)
  Subject: Parenting, Families, Community, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Parents of Los Angeles (GLPLA)
- GLSTN (The Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Teachers Network) (Box 4)
  Subject: Education, Gay, Lesbian, Community
  Publisher: The Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Teachers Network
- GMHC Recreation News (Gay Men's Health Crisis) (Box 4)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Community, Gay, Gay male, Health
  Publisher: Gay Men's Health Crisis
- Going Places In Florida (Box 4)
  Subject: News, Community, Gay, Gay male, 1970s, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Albe's Gifts Inc.
  Publication City: Pierre Station, Miami, FL
- Golden Gate Business Association (GGBA): Buyer's Guide & Directory (Box 4)
  Subject: Directory, Business, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Golden Gate Business Association
- Good Times Bookshop Catalog (Box 4)
  Subject: Literary, Catalog, Books, Book reviews
  Publisher: The Good Times Bookshop
  Publication City: Port Jefferson, NY
- GP Reporter, The (Gay Press Association) (Box 4)
  Subject: Mass media, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, News, Community, Politics
  Publisher: Gay Press Association
- Grand Union, The (Newsletter of the New York City Union of Lesbians and Gay Men) (Box 4)
  Subject: 1980s, Community, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: The New York City Union of Lesbians and Gay Men
  Publication City: Brooklyn, NY
- Gray Pride Chicago Newsletter (Box 4)
  Subject: Aged
- Great Outdoors San Diego (Box 4)
  Publication City: (San Diego)
- Green LIght (Quarterly Newsletter of the Dartmouth Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association) (Box 4)
  Subject: College/University, Education, Dartmouth College, Community, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: The Darthmouth Gay & Lesbian Alumni Association (Dartmouth GALA)
- GUARD News (Gays United to Attack Repression & Discrimination) (Box 4)
  Subject: Anti-violence, Lesbian, Gay, Queer, Community, News, Politics, 1990s, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Gays United to Attack Repression & Discrimination
  Publication City: Ft. Lauderdale, FL
- Guelph Gay Equality (GGE) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, International, Canada, News, Community, Community service
  Publisher: Guelph Gay Equality
  Publication City: Guelph, ON
- Guide for '69, The (Vagabond World Guide) (Box 4)
  Subject: Travel, Directory, Gay, Gay male, Community, International
  Publisher: Vagabond World Guide
- Guide: International Northwest Magazine of Gay/Lesbian Life (Box 4)
  Publication City: (Seattle, WA)
- Guild Gazette (A Monthly News Journal Sponsored by the Tampa Bay Business Guild) (Box 4)
  Subject: Business, News, Community, Legal, Politics, Gay, Gay male, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Tampa Bay Business Guild
  Publication City: Tampa Bay, FL
- GVA Newsletter (Gay Veterans Association) (Box 4)
  Subject: Veterans, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Gay male, News, Community, Legal
  Publisher: Gay Veterans Association
- GWARM Moniter (Gay and Women's Alliance for Resposible Media) (Box 4)
  Subject: Mass media, 1970s, Lesbian, Gay, Gay male, Gay liberation movement, News, Community, Women, Men, Feminist
  Publisher: Gay and Women's Alliance for Responsible Media (GWARM)
- H Inc. (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay male, Community, Entertainment, 1990s
  Publisher: Quest Publishing (DPBBB Enterprises, Inc.)
  Publication City: Denver, CO
- HA NEWS (The Official Newsletter of Homosexuals Anonymous Fellowship Services) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Gay male, Lesbian, Religious, Therapy, Psychology, 1990s, Ex-Gay
  Publisher: Homosexuals Anonymous Fellowship Services (HAFS)
  Publication City: Reading, PA
- Hale (Box 4)
  Publisher: (Gay People's Union of the University of Wisconsin)
  Publication City: (Stevens Point, WI)
- Hampton Roads GLBVA Newsletter (Gay Lesbian Bisexual Veterans Association) (Box 4)
  Subject: Veterans, Gay, Lesbian, Occupation Based Organizations
  Publisher: Hampton Roads GLBVA (Gay Lesbian Bisexual Veterans Association)
  Publication City: Norfolk, VA
- Hawaii Gay Community News (Gay Community Center Hawaii) (Box 4)
  Publisher: Gay Community Center (Hawaii)
- Health Care for All (Box 4)
- Health Crisis Network (HCN) Newsnotes (Box 4)
  Subject: Health, HIV/AIDS, Occupation Based Organizations, Gay
  Publisher: Health Crisis Network
- Healthlines (AIDS Report Subscription) (Box 4)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, News, 1980s
  Publisher: Healthlines
  Publication City: Williamsville, NY
- HER SAY (Box 4)
  Subject: Women, Feminist, News, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: Women's News Institute
- HG (High Tech Gays Newsletter) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Business, 1980s
  Publisher: High Tech Gays
  Publication City: San Jose, CA
- HI! (Newsletter of Homosexuals Intransigent! / New York) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, 1970s, Gay male, Men, News, Zine
  Publisher: Homosexuals Intransigent!
- Him (Box 4)
  Subject: Physique
- Hits & Misses (Women's Boxing) (Box 4)
  Subject: Sports, Women, News, 1970s
  Publisher: Hits and Misses
  Publication City: Hollywood, CA
- HIV Advisor (Critical Care America) (Box 4)
  Subject: Humor, Health, HIV/AIDS, Politics, Occupation Based Organizations, 1990s, Men, Women
  Publisher: Critical Care America
  Publication City: Westborough, MA
- HIV Bulletin, The (Office of HIV Services, Inova Health System) (Box 4)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, Community services, News
  Publisher: Office of HIV Services, Inova Health System
  Publication City: Fairfax, VA
- HIV New Mexico (HIV Coordinating Council of New Mexico) (Box 4)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, News
  Publisher: HIV Coordinating Council New Mexico, New Mexico Association of People Living With AIDS
  Publication City: Santa Fe, NM
- HIV/AIDS Project News: Report on Project Resources and Activities (National Conference of State Legislatures) (Box 4)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, Occupation Based Organizations, Politics, 1990s
  Publisher: National Conference of State Legislatures
- Hold Hands (Box 4)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Directory, News
  Publisher: Gay Activists Alliance of New Jersey, Inc.
  Publication Country: Unted States
  Publication City: South Hackensack, NJ
- Homosexual Citizen, The (Mattachine Society of Washington) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, News, Lesbian, Legal, Politics, 1950s
  Publisher: Mattachine Society of Washington
  Publication City: Washington, DC
- Homosexual Information Center Newsletter (Box 4)
  Subject: Health, Gay, Lesbian, News, History, Book review, Community
  Publisher: Homosexual Information Center
- Homosexual Renaissance (Publication of Homosexual Intransignet!) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, News, 1960s, 1970s
  Publisher: Homosexual Intransigent!
- Honolulu Weekly (Box 4)
  Subject: Alternative local newspaper, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Families, News
  Publisher: Honolulu Weekly, Inc.
- Hoot 'N Howl Modesto (Box 4)
  Subject: 1970s, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian, News, Legal, Politics, Anti-violence, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: Modesto Hoot 'N Howl
  Publication City: Modesto, CA
- Hot Lines (Newsletter of the Gay & Lesbian Information Center) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, News, 1980s
  Publisher: Gay & Lesbian Information Center
  Publication City: Lorain, OH
- Hotspots! (Atlanta's Hotspots) (Box 4)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Classifieds, 1990s
  Publisher: Rox Publishing, Inc.
- HQ (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Politics, College/University, Literary, Harvard University, 1990s
  Publisher: HQ Magazine
- HRGALA Newsletter (Hampton Roads Gay And Lesbian Alliance) (Box 4)
  Publisher: Hampton Roads Gay And Lesbian Alliance (HRGALA)
  Publication City: Virginia Beach, VA
- Human Sexuality Update (Box 4)
  Subject: Education, Health, Therapy, Directory, Occupation Based Organizations, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Men, Women, Heterosexual, Education
  Publisher: The Haworth Press, Inc.
- Hyacinths and Biscuits (Box 4)
  Subject: Literary, Zine, 1970s
  Publisher: Hyacinths and Biscuits
  Publication City: Brea, CA
- I Know You Know (Box 4)
  Publisher: Jernan Ltd. Inc.
- Identity Northview (News and Views for Alaska's Gay and Lesbian Community) (Box 4)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, College/University, Education
  Publisher: Identity Inc.
  Publication City: Anchorage, AK
- If the Shoe Fits (Box 4)
- IFGE Newsletter (International Foundation for Gender Education) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gender issues, Transgender, 2000s, Health, Medicine, Transsexual
  Publisher: International Foundation for Gender Education
- IFO-LEOFFRCO (Gay Police Officers) (Box 4)
  Subject: Occupation Based Organizations, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: IFO-LEOFFERCO
- IGA Bulletin (International Association of Lesbians/Gay Women and Gay men) (Box 4)
  Subject: International
- IGBO Newsletter (Bowling) (Box 4)
  Subject: Sports, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: IGBO (Bowling)
- IGLYO - bulletin (Box 4)
  Publisher: (International Gay & Lesbian Youth Organization)
  Publication Country: (Norway)
  Publication City: (Oslo)
- ILIS Newsletter (International Lesbian Information Service) (Box 4)
  Subject: Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: International Lesbian Information Service
  Publication Country: Norway
  Publication City: Oslo
- Image (San Francisco Examiner magazine) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, 1990s
  Publisher: San Francisco Examiner
  Publication City: San Fracisco, CA
- Impact: Journal of National Family Sex Education Week (Institute of Family Research and Education) (Box 4)
  Publication City: Syracuse, NY
- Impart (Monthly Newsletter of Fargo-Moorhead Area, Dignity/Lutherans Concerned) (Box 4)
  Subject: Religious: Lutheran, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Dignity/ Lutherans Concerned
  Publication City: Moorhead, ND
- Imperio G (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay male, Gay, Entertainment, 2000s
  Publication Country: Argentina
  Publication City: Buenos Aires
- In (Box 4)
  Subject: Erotica
  Publisher: (All Star Processing, Inc.)
  Publication City: (San Francisco)
- In Full View (Overlooked Opinions) (Box 4)
  Subject: News, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian
- In The Life (Box 4)
- In the Life (Gay & Lesbian Issues and Culture on National Public Television) (Box 4)
  Subject: Television, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, 2000s
  Publisher: Life Media, Inc.
- In Your Face! (Box 4)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Gay male, Transgender, Literary, News, 1990s
- Index 6 (French and English Language) (Box 4)
  Subject: Directory, Cruising, Gay, Gay male
  Publisher: Les Publications Sortie Inc.
- Indiana Word, The (Box 4)
  Subject: Alternative local newpaper, News, Gay, Gay male, Lesbian, Religious: Jewish, 1990s
- Infoblatt de Schwulen Sportvereins (German Language) (Box 4)
  Subject: Sports, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publication City: Berlin
- Informher, The (Produced by the Friday Night Womyn's Group) (Box 4)
  Subject: Women, Lesbian, News, 1990s
  Publisher: Friday Night Womyn's Group
- Inside OutCharlotte (OutCharlotte's Newsletter) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay arts, Gay, Gay male, Lesbian, Performing arts, News, 2000s
  Publisher: OutCharlotte
  Publication City: Charlotte, NC
- Inside QGLU (News from Queens Gays & Lesbians United, Inc.) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, News, 2000s
  Publisher: Queens Gays & Lesbians United, Inc.
  Publication City: Long Island City, NY
- Insider, The (Society for Individual Rights) (Box 4)
  Subject: News, Gay, Lesbian, 1970s
  Publisher: Society foir Individual Rights
- Institute for Rational Living and Institute for Rational-Emotive Therapy (Box 4)
  Subject: Psychology, Therapy, 1970s, Health, Women, Men
  Publisher: The Institute for Rational Living
- Institute for the Study of Human Resources (A Study of 388 North American Homosexual Males: Preliminary Findings [ONE Institute]) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay male, Gay, News, Gay journal, 1960s, Gay, Lesbian, Transgender, Psychology, Medicine, Gender issues
  Publisher: Institute for the Study of Human Resources
  Publication Country: Untied States
- Inter/View (Andy Warho's Film Magazine) (Box 4)
  Subject: Entertainment, News, 1970s, Mass media
  Publisher: INTER VIEW, Inc.
- Interaction (AIDS National Interfaith Network) (Box 4)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Religious, 1990s
  Publisher: AIDS National Interfaith Network
- International Women's Tribune Centre Newsletter (Box 4)
  Subject: Women, Feminist, 1980s
  Publisher: International Women's Tribune Centre
- Invert (The Journal of Gay & Lesbian Sensibility) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Entertainment, Mass media
  Publisher: Alternatives: The Gay & Lesbian Cultural Organization, Inc.
  Publication City: West Hartford, CT
- It's About Time (Newsletter of the NLFO [National Lesbian Feminist Organization]) (Box 4)
  Subject: Feminist, Lesbian, 1970s, Women, Lesbian separatists
  Publisher: National Lesbian Feminist Organization (NLFO)
- It's Your Move (An Action-Information Report from CGRO) (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, Politics
  Publisher: (Coalition for Gay Rights in Ontario)
- IYG Reachout (Indiana Youth Group Newsletter) (Box 4)
  Subject: Youth, Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender
  Publisher: Indianna Youth Group (IYG)
- Jamaica Gaily News (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, 1970s
  Publisher: Gay Freedom Movement